So, hello everyone, in this section we are going to work with this profile, so in the styles
beginner I have actually pasted all of the starter code, okay, so we don't have to waste
time on this one, just copy it from here and paste it in your profile page, okay.
So, this one it is already imported one FAQ camera icon from the React icons, and another
thing is that since we are going to use the author store, so let's import that also,
the author store from the double dot slash store slash author store, now what we are going
to do is in this one, actually we are going to import the log user, so log user equals
to author store, we are going to destructure it and get it from the author store, okay, so for
this a log user we are going to get several things, like we are going to take the profile
picture right, so in this profile picture what we are going to do is go down here and in
this one, source image source equals to, we are going to set it as logged user dot profile
pick profile, pick, okay, control and as safe, and there are several other things also,
so I kept these fields as blank, okay, so like this is the user name and for this one
it is actually email, okay, so we are going to set this also, so what we are going to
do is here just take the data from the log user, so log user dot user name, okay, and for
this one here we are going to take the email, so log user dot email, okay, control and
as safe, and after this we also need to handle that on submit change right, so in this
input as we can see that it is going to accept all kind of images, that is why we have
kept several things like id equal to profile of the type equal to file class name equal
to hidden and except equal to image slash star, so it is going to accept all the images,
now on change, so on change equals to handle profile upload, so this will be going to be
one submit function, okay, so once you click that button you will need to go through
this function, so let us create this also, so const handle profile upload equals to take
the ES event callback function, now instead of that const file equals to e dot target dot
files, and we are going to get this from the 0th index, and let us declare one reader,
so const reader equals to a new file reader, file reader, and after this reader dot read
as data URL, okay, and we are going to take that file, whatever we get, okay, so control
as it is going to save this thing, and we have changed everything right, let us review
profile pick, okay, right, so and handle profile upload also, and use log user dot username
log user dot email, okay, okay, right, now go inside this auth store, since we need to make
that profile page function right, so we need to go to this auth store, and just add one
comma here, and make the function, so update profile, update profile async, and we are going
to take the data, and after that one callback function, and inside of this we are going to declare
one response variable, so const res equals to, um, await whatever the data which is going
to come through xcs instance, so extends instance dot post, so whenever the user is going
to hit this route auth slash update dash profile, then we are going to set the log user
to response dot data, so it is going to take the response, okay, and set it, and then
after that we are going to take this toast, and send the success, and it is going to just
say that profile, profile updated success fully, okay, I think this would be fine, so it
is going to save this once again, there is some problem with the mouse, okay, cut this one,
okay, so response dot data, okay, data is declared but the value is never used, why it is
saying like that, I think some glitch, no issues once again, let me check it once again,
so, I had made some mistake, foolish mistake, actually log user res dot data, and we had
to send the data here, that I forgot, that is why it was showing some error, okay, so
that is it, we have successfully sent the data also, now we can test those things, okay,
but before that what we are actually going to do is, okay, one more error is showing, why
it is showing here, update profile, no, we do not need this, so, remove this one, now save
it, and now let us go to this profile page, now what we are going to do is, we take this
reader, and we apply this on load, like, on load method, and async, after this async,
we have a wait update profile, we are going to take that update profile, and then we are
just going to take the profile pick from the reader, so reader dot result, let us save
this one, so now I think it would be working fine, let us,